[Music]
[Laughter]
welcome once again to the natatorium at
the Nanjing Olympic sports center we
could be seeing double here in the final
of the women's 3-meter springboard
competition
Liu Sheng ping is on course second gold
of these hoof Olympic Games if she could
add the 3 meter crowd and a 10 meter
title
she will emulate the achievements of Lin
ul four years ago in Singapore who also
landed a gold and diamond supported this
event right from the first competition
China in such a great tradition in
diving of course and there enjoyed great
success as well so no wonder the numbers
have turned out
that's the schedule it's the women's
3-meter springboard final third final so
far in this competition
12 contestants will go
well those every choice we could see a
repeat of the platform one two three
here on the 3-meter springboard
it's the final divers from Ukraine to
USA will certainly have other ideas then
another Chinese victory a good crowd in
once again reminder on field position
after the preliminary competition where
we watched nine rounds of diving the
first five rounds were limited to a
total degree of difficulty of nine point
five and those marks are carried forward
into this final here is the dive order
which doesn't reflect those points and
carried over rather these callings from
the whole overall competition Liu Sheng
ping the one to beat and I've goal over
and low also were medalists at 10 meters
nine rounds in the preliminary
competition so a demanding schedule for
these girls just four rounds for them to
go through again no limit on these days
we've got the NBA player there yapping
distinctive figure in China of course
nice fish
gap between the
to Larry
a big test of a magnet is reshaping
nasty messages
well oops confidence she should be
just waiting for the signal
first up is Saira Karolina Perez Beltran
of Colombia just coming through those
movements
good atmosphere here in the arena such a
great facility really
setting for this competition
it's a big spotlight for these young
teenagers
so the first round
for me mm
not settle down let's hope the dollar
discount
here
small realms after this that's a patriot
three sevens decent stop
young Molly Carlson 50
Avenger
very tidy
she's been the Pan American junior
champion in 2013 this has been a big
test for her
[Music]
59:40 that's a decent start
if you have mass from this mission
divers hitting a bit of form
what about entry
[Music]
give me the box away 36.5
eighteen years of age
yeah
[Applause]
little bit untidy
[Music]
opening with a 3.0 she's got quite a big
program of times
[Applause]
she won bronze at the qualifying event
very nice pint position
63 points she's changed this dive from
the pike to tuck which is a lesser
degree of difficulty didn't go too well
for her in the preliminary this dive and
see what you can do now
and other divers have
there are after the preliminary
competition to change a dive and this
could have been a good decision
she's in contention for a medal if she
gets into some good form
very good decision 3/8
in a couple of good free dives in the
preliminary competition and a couple of
disappointing ones
committed totally to that
plenty of height of the board
just a little bit and turn around the
edges especially in that entry
[Music]
- now our somersault tucked completed
this dive quite tidally in preliminary
competition
[Applause]
well she had two decent times and two
rather poor ones needs to find
consistency and she could challenge for
a medal
[Music]
II know I know
they would too long hot summer sucked
[Applause]
just falls away from their form entry
three sevens 5678
[Music]
with a real chance of repeating silver
from 10 meters here at three meters
[Applause]
needs to be consistent right the way
through
that's a biggest tariff dive
and a decent effort 6750
[Music]
and that's good
let's go lock up the deep fold 3.5
somersault
just a bit untidy around the edges
now here comes the stop
listen to people's going to that second
gold medal
[Applause]
you
[Music]
and would consolidating her position at
the top of the leaderboard low and
kresnik doing very well
you
[Music]
there is Beltran
in wood - I'm so pumped
360s
[Music]
fifteen year olds of Molly Carson ranked
seven which would be an encouragement
for her trying to encourage her all the
way good height
it could have been smoother well that's
more than better efforts
done
[Music]
maybe in bounce Switzerland
[Applause]
[Music]
it's a very steady dive
three similar lives
[Music]
Lindau of sweden now forward to now some
salt one twist
just a little bit on the untidy side she
really commits to her died cell powerful
figure
really does need to tidy up the details
though
should be rather disappointed with 34.5
[Music]
so in good Olivera picks up her score
thirty-seven point two zero for that
forward three and a half somersault and
we now move on to Ukraine's first nor
Schulich and she will be attempting a
forward two and a half somersault two
point four degree of difficulty there's
the Ukraine coach looking a little bit
anxiously and have to say but she has
performed well throughout the
competition so far
a century super entry therefore Ghana
for Ukraine and that 1:05 be died gives
us the forward two and a half somersault
that's the code word height and you can
hear probably the scores in the
background eights and sevens good entry
should be happy with that fifty seven
point six zero then for the Ukrainian
girl it's in contention and as we moved
now to Italy's Laura Velata the lotto
with a forward two and a half somersault
with one twist
lots of hikes involved in this a little
bit overcooked on the entry but a good
effort from vallata
so what the judges think about that but
she gets good height
most of the rotation done before she
comes past the board and enters the
water just a little bit untidily
[Music]
you can hear reflected in the scores
there
six and a half six is there in the six
and a half fifty five point five then
she's ranked three total 301 good scores
for Laura balata of Italy we're in now
with Gracia Layden Mahoney of the USA
she'll be going backwards two and a half
somersault with tucks
I could throw tations in fact over the
top of the board and then the moment she
came underneath it was a little bit fast
in fact over rotation when she didn't
need it she needed to open up a fraction
earlier you can see that extra bit of
splash
fresh young lady
only then 54.6 he opened a second
position so doing really well here the
sick around his schneider of germany 2.8
degree of difficulty and that means it's
a back two and a half somersault again
in the tough position so same dive as
we've just witnessed see whether or not
she can open a bit earlier
good concentration and a similar kind of
problem went on that entry mild applause
from this natatorium here at the Olympic
sports center good close position in the
air very tidy in the air but just that
entry a little bit overcooked they even
see a little bit of extra splash and the
judges risk its fond with a scores a
forty six point two back in seventh rank
two nine four point eight zero then for
Schneider now this is very interesting
the Malaysian girl CIE lo CIE has been
superb throughout the competition here
107 see that means a forward three and a
half somersault with tucks here we go
lovely just a maybe a little under the
vertical for the entry but they really
like the look of this girl she's been
working so well a Malaysian diving has
come of age for the last decade or so a
little bit off to the side there at the
entry but she really has put together
very very impressive performance
there you go three thirty five point
seven zero ranked 1 at the moment 54.6
for that one slightly disappointing
Mexico now with Alejandra or rocks call
Rosa she's got a back two and a half
somersault
needs that real height off the floor
which it gets well and again just a
little extra splash for that sir got the
approval of the coach which is the most
important thing again nice height and
then just a little bit of extra movement
in the air which you didn't quite knee
just have a look at the opening up of
the hips going forward yeah and there
was trying to adjust in the air as an
extraordinary ability these divers have
adjusting the air for the entry 5460
that puts her in bronze medal position
at the moment 3:15 and now well there's
something special there is always in
competitions and here we see it once
again rule shrimp and she's gonna do a
backward two and a half somersault 18
years old and I tell you she is quite
phenomenal she knows where she is
exactly in the air all the time despite
the speed of rotation watch out
and they gain good entry I don't know
whether you noticed but there was that
moment where she's visualizing the dive
her eyes are closed and just before she
goes for it and that is the moment where
she says feels wow this is the moment
we're going to open up get the entry and
just listen to the scores come through
that's a strong strong died she will
take over the lead right here no doubt
at all there you go right 12.8
difficulty eight and eight point five
sixty eight point six zero wall jumping
does what is expected of her there she
is at the top of the table Malaysia's
low Jie in second and Fresno Chile Ghana
Ghana crash knowledge first notice
leaked from Ukraine is in third position
overall a moment
the atmosphere around the Nanjing
natatorium is really really exciting
they know they've got a home crowd
favorite here is there's nothing that
brings an atmosphere to life like a very
very popular and very impressive
favorite but here's Sarah Karolina Perez
Beltran preparing the board again for
her new dive that'll be a back two and a
half somersault terms of the
performances before we had the German
girl actually coming up four places from
that the last time Schneider Josephine
Schneider so a really good performance
56.7 for a first-time 46 for a second
and then the third one 71-65 very
impressive here we go
third dive and that was just under
rotated there was very very unlucky for
Beltran so the back two and a half
somersault just have a look at it she
goes too early with the open up and
there she just doesn't make it off to
the side a little bit as well
unfortunate look good from the start and
now it's going to be under for under
fives I think and listen to this cause
of this
thirty two point two zero three fifteen
altogether it was too tough a time for
her to execute and is the youngster
Molly Carlson very young and things are
just 15 I'm not mistaken and certainly
enjoying her first out experience here
for Canada third place back for two and
a half somersaults big concentration
again going through the motions before
she actually executes the diet it's so
close to being a very good dive but you
will definitely be marked down for that
entry you can see that extra splash this
is what the Chinese girls don't do they
really know where they are in the air
and their timing of opening is perfect
[Music]
thirty-six point four zero then four
fives and a four so Vivian bath now
from Switzerland she gets a really good
cheer there's a lot of Swiss supporters
inside this natatorium can she keep her
concentration backward two and a half
somersaults again a two point eight
difficulty it's the toughest she takes
on entry is everything father is a coach
and the game doesn't quite make it he's
happy though and as long as dad is happy
I guess you can say you've given it your
best you can tell if that extra splash
it's so so important you enter like a
knife coming into the water you can't
create so much and expect to have top
scores for five four five four zero 36.4
she's got a good total though thirty
three hundred and thirty five here's
Linda of Sweden
ironical in doubt this will be also back
to an hour somersault same degree of
difficulty she's 11th overall before
this dive
and another one that just didn't quite
execute at the end everything that
happens above the board there is good
looks solid and then the opening and the
delivery not quite there should be
marked down once again just looks so
good until that moment it's overcooked
on rotation if the scores coming up
thirty five together 320 in total and
again four fives and fours it's not good
enough if you want to get up into the
[Music]
big big dive required here's a degree of
difficulty of three forward two and a
half somersaults one twist this is huge
so difficult good girl oh yes English de
Oliveira came up with certainly the best
dive of this round so far watch this
great height beautiful movement in the
air and then the open up she saw the
water early and look at the finish very
nice
we've got seven and a six five so
that'll score well
there's the confirmation of the score
right now good girl sixty three points
three sixty two point three five seven
all around they must be very happy with
that
Barbara's elf scanner fresh nah she leak
she is trying now forward two and a half
somersaults again with Pike's so hip
extension very very important here
in third place at the moment can she
improve on that position
into it twice now
can she deliver it's a great die
oh yes the back two and a half
somersault 2.8 degree of difficulty just
certainly stand a chance here of holding
the bronze if not improving score but
that 391 90 takes the first position at
the moment 57.4 for the dive itself so
excellent work from blessed Noreen oh
that's not Shirley she's in seventh
place before this diet 55.5 she had for
the last one was a forward two and a
half now ship we've got reverse watch
the reverse movement here for 2.80 and a
good ever except tied in those heels
just came over a fraction didn't cut
through the water and she would have
liked but it's a good aerial movement
landing just a little bit extra you see
again it's got a good degree of
difficulty so
53.2 takes enough into bronze at the
moment although we know we've got some
high-quality diverse still to come
Trisha Layton Mahoney from Massachusetts
in the United States and I'm sure
they'll all be watching all her friends
have Powell's
or relatives it's a wonderful
opportunity for these young people to
show how dedicated they are to their
sport it's a reverse two and a half
somersault nicely done oh and much
better than last time but back two and a
half didn't work the reverse two and a
half certainly did that was very good
indeed just look at again the control
above the board the opening out very
nice entry - look at that hardly a spout
so yeah seven
fifth at the moment will this improve
her position sixty-three dead takes it
up into seven levels 375 points point
eight zero so that's a really good die
that would have done a no harm at all
the American girl Horatio later Mahoney
we now move forward to Germany and the
useffin Schneider from Dresden she was
involved in the 12th 12th Youth World
Championships 2012 couple of years ago
and again she asked overplayed her hand
on the rotation but it was a good
attempt there by Schneider reversed two
and a half somersaults she improved last
time I'm not sure that the entry will do
any favors he was just a little bit off
the vertical here
you'll be marked down for that entry as
well I think there you go 45 all
together ranked 6-3 39.8 just as
expected so the Malaysian girl she's
called Joey no Joey
Kuala Lumpur Malaysia they have made
great strides in their diving of course
we know their success has bred success
and they've got a whole string of good
divers coming through very strongly
certainly favorites for the Southeast
Asian Games next year maybe we'll be
contesting the Asian Games in a while as
well here we go back two and a half
somersaults land it oh yes oh well
Southeast Asia can be proud of that one
that back two and a half somersault
entry was absolutely super look at that
hardly a smidgen of a splash
good work I'm just listening to the
score seven eights and a half eight it
will be big look at that sixty-three and
low Charlie thinks the three ninety
eight point seven zero and look at the
coaching loving it you have to say well
done brilliant coaches one yeah I like
some Alejandra bigger pardon Oh Rose
Scott looser is up now
she comes from jealous Co and this one
is an inward two and a half somersault
again it's all about the timing of the
entry and again he just over plays her
hand a little bit so tough and it's so
easy for me to sit here and suggest that
she could have done a lot better I'm
sure she would think that she could have
done better itself but everything was
good until the entry
you can understand how the judges are
looking at this cartoon look at that
thirty-six point four zero back in
ranked sixth position overall four and a
half we knew it was going to be that now
can this young lady get up into the
eighth and ninth right here she is from
Nanjing wall jumping it's no wonder that
she's bringing the clouds in it's
fantastic
she's from one wall high school and
who's here is a coach let's have a look
at this reversed two and a half
somersaults haha what do you think you
reckon that this is popular around here
you betcha just look at it it was the
wide tucks to start and then she closes
up and it's a pert look at that closes
up for the entry it's beautiful just
have a listen and look at this response
from the judges sixty four point four
sevens and one eight there in fact the
several age they were discounted of
course the degree of difficulty but that
after three rounds here is the score
Lucien thing the local girl 4:30 she's
definitely going to be uncatchable here
for thirty point five low je the
Malaysian in second place and continuing
in third place overall is the Ukrainian
girl Prez nor Sheila
so this is now your all-important fourth
round the one that decides the medals
and you have to say that every single
one of these girls has not only had a
fabulous introduction to feed time
competition but they have contributed
enormous ly to the success of the Youth
Olympic Games it's been stunning
watching them perform but also
interacting as well
the atmosphere is fabulous here's now
Sarah Carolyn Perez Beltran she comes
from Colombia and the coach is fun come
full Sun out the reverse two and a half
somersaults it doesn't quite stick on
entry the tucks they're just a little
wayward but again she would have learnt
so much from this experience they've now
got some real footage to work on a
little bit off the side you see the
vertical position was not held came a
little bit to the side and that was the
result lots of water
so here's a score thirty point eight
zero thirty three hundred and forty five
point eight of the overall position Mali
calcining invited here from Thunder Bay
in Canada and certainly a lot of people
will be looking to her for the future
she is a young girl some good
experiences at the plan Americans last
year gold there so she has got huge
potential and again just a little bit
undercooked it but that reverse
two-and-a-half somersault it certainly
will be scoring reasoning while there
was no disaster there
that was the lunch you just opened a
little bit late and then kept on
rotating in the vertical position which
is not a good idea when you're diving
instead of a look at her scores then
coming up shortly yes she is
but she's had a wonderful experience
forty three point four zero then three
eighty eight in total jumps to the top
of the tree for the moment just after
two competitors so Vivian bath right now
that they know in Switzerland they call
a BB BB there's a bit of life in that
there's no question about that
yep and her father is her coach so the
back one-and-a-half somersaults one and
a half twists
nice oh yes very good it's a two point
four degree of difficulty he likes it a
lot of these parent coaches obviously
living their own dreams through their
offspring but I tell you right there
that's the best spring right there it
said fact one and a half summers one
laughs - it's very nice entry a little
bit low on the degree of difficulty but
the execution will definitely score well
let's have a listen there you go in the
70s it was very very good let's have the
graphic now forty-eight and three
hundred and eighty three point seven
zero he's a happy chappy you can tell
Swedish girl Veronica Linda
she's back again still in 11th place so
anything will bring her up the ladder
into the 10th position and Beyond will
be great oh yeah well almost complete it
was just not full right there a little
bit too much rotation that Ford three
and a half somersault that's what we've
got to emphasize three and a half times
she's in the air we're on the
springboard here this is not the
10-meter we've got to get huge height to
accomplish that 2.8 degree of difficulty
almost got the entry great there in
vertical position but there we go sixes
and sevens they're discounted couple of
them almost got it really perfect 50
3.20 in total then sixes and the cup and
one seven there
so Rosie's it has Ingrid de Oliveira
back two and a half somersaults this is
a difficult dive everybody 3.0 the same
as a second third dive terms of
difficulty
lots of bouncing and she didn't fly it
make it did cheek she didn't make those
pikes it's a much easier obviously when
you get into tucks once you've got those
long levers really really needing to
rotate it so tough didn't quite get it
over the top lid sheet and failed with
the vertical entry you could tell why
she was jumping on the board to start
with though she needed absolutely
everything in height in order to
accomplish it difficult dive she'll be
marked down to the entry but yeah 30
altogether threes and 3.5 that's tough
let you gamble you take the risk if it
doesn't come off it's tough right and
there's gonna crash nosh Schulich
apologies for having trouble with her
name before she's from the national
university of physical training and
ukraine can be proud of this young girl
italian she's really really impressive
ah lovely Oh reverse two-and-a-half
somersaults 2.8 degree of difficulty and
I tell you what the Ukrainian coaches do
not wear their hearts on their sleeves
very often
he must be absolutely delighted as far
as he's concerned that is perfection
good girl that is excellent third place
you might even push the Malaysian girl
gie lo jolly would have looked at that
and thought oh my goodness I really am
sort of full out the stops rate that
could be the bronze medal dive let's
never listen to it 67 point - good girl
four fifty nine ten absolutely stunning
well done
Laura the lot are known as oulala
and of course we've got the mascots
here's known as Lily so Lola will get a
lily if she gets any further down the
line here first the new European junior
champion championships in 2013 so Laura
balata of Italy backward two and a half
somersaults 2.8 and another good attempt
there that 2.8 see the big difference
between that and de Oliveira was that
she was doing tucks with a somersaults
as opposed to pikes it makes it a little
bit easier and of course you could get
right over into the entry position very
much easier good girl Laura Bilotta
probably heard the scores there six and
a half six is fifty four point six up
into second position over all of them I
went four hundred and nine points coach
Brooks smugly impressed by that okay
Gracie Layden Mahoney from the United
States is up next
so like gymnastics ice hockey you can
tell and lacrosse and ballet and soccer
my goodness me the all-round athlete
Gracia Layden Mahoney us a reverse
one-and-a-half somersaults two and a
half twist 2.9 degree of difficulty it's
all action here yeah
and the thing should be pretty pleased
with that we are in the women's 3-meter
springboard final and you have to say
we've done the halfway in the final
round and it's all now boiling up to
really really impressive finish here
good girl she really completed that the
twist and the somersaults very very well
it's a good score all together with the
DD there's a great of difficulty
it's 53.65 for twenty nine point four
five and a high five there from the
coach right Pynchon Ida
see whether or not she can improve she
dropped back a little bit there back in
Knights at the moment forward two and a
half somersaults one twist Oh didn't
quite make the entry but all the
elements were there for the dive so it's
it will be pretty well judged with a
game it is that absolutely all-important
entry that makes such a difference and
she was underneath it wasn't she didn't
quite have the speed for the entry she
gets I was going to say if she gets five
she'll be lucky but they are undefined
there you go forty point five and 380
takes her into seventh place ranked at
the moment and now this is an
all-important one currently second
position low gie of Malaysia and it was
a brave brave effort earlier by the
Ukrainian girl but here this is an
all-important back one and a half
somersault one and a half twist two
point four degree of difficulty not a
high degree of difficulty so the
execution the entry in the water
absolutely vital and a little bit over
the top just a smidgen not much that it
looks like Ukraine will be celebrating
that one I don't know nice moment
therefore as Xiao Yi she says thank you
to the judges and to the crowd and that
flung Chiang I'm not sure he'll be happy
with this because it was a two point
four degree of difficulty and the entry
just a little bit overcooked with the
heels wasn't it you can just feel this
you're a bit anxious it's never listened
to the scores
oh I don't think it's quite good enough
if number - yeah it's number two at the
top there so 48 altogether and I knew
there was going to be a little bit of
problem there for low jolly it is in
fact the Ukrainian girl who's come up
there Ghana Christ no Sheila who has
come up now - a very very good position
where she's still leading with one to go
seventh overall at the moment Alejandro
or Oscar looser she is the Mexican girl
with a forward two and a half somersault
one twist and again just a little bit
under the vertical that will be marked
down but a brave effort because that's a
3.0 degree of difficulty yeah fabulous
finish right okay this is the one it
looks very much at the moment lo sha Yi
the Malaysian has got into bronze medal
position as know she really has come up
into silver medal position because there
will be no chance I'm sure when Walsh
anything comes to the board there is the
score forty six point five zero she's
come up into fifth ranked at the moment
but of course well after Walsh and ping
has performed her dive that will drop it
back into six so good work for the
Mexican but this is what it's all about
the final dive again it's a very easy
dive relatively back one-and-a-half
somersault one and a half twist the girl
from Nanjing will set us alive with a
gold medal performance right here final
dark 3-meter springboard for women gold
medal dive
oh my goodness you want it simple you
want it beautiful you want it controlled
wall Changqing is definitely the real
deal and rules here will be happy with
that she showed us applause and that
cutaway and just look at these replays
dream performances all round perfect
position in the air and look at the
entry this is how you dive the eights
and the eight and a half it just tells
the world we've now seen another Olympic
Youth Olympic champion here in the pool
sixty one point two it's been a
fantastic performance we are going to
see a smile in a moment and certainly
smiles all round I'm sure very very
impressive
the Malaysian the coach there will be
just celebrating a medal not quite a
silver commiserate he is the Ukrainian
coach as well because he has picked up
the silver with his Ghana press no
Schlick and there's the final scores
whoosh amping absolutely perform to
perfection for 9205 takes the gold Ghana
crush Naz which takes the silver and low
je takes the Bronx
so all the other performances there
Ingrid Oliveira came up very nicely as
well it has been a fabulous contest has
been loads of really really high-end
performances and of course with these
girls being put on the on the podium in
terms of the spotlight
it's a really really difficult thing to
continue to put on your you know top
performance with it knowing that not
just a cloud and have the expectations
for the people at home because we are
going worldwide with our coverage here
the use Olympic Games in nineteen
through fourteen Lily comes out to greet
the cloud again and in fact I read that
she was designed on the colourful
pebbles that on the shorelines around
here so that shows the likes skimming
across the water well there won't be too
much skimming at the moment there's
afternoon with them but certainly the
cameras will be picking them up and just
a couple of moments and delighting the
children I'm sure it's been a fantastic
time for all of us here in Nanjing in
every sport we've seen fabulous
performances that we've also seen some
extraordinary camaraderie
some wonderful new relationships
developing and of course the ambitions
of the IOC to promote
you
we did a housekeeping work going on
inside the natatorium here in the
Olympic sports center I was preparing
for the presentation in just a moment
it is quite remarkable the way that
China's diving expertise has come to the
fore I well remember back in Barcelona
92 being on Moz week and seeing
Wilmington putting up an extraordinary
performance into the what appeared to be
the city's Cathedral the Sagrada famlia
it was absolutely amazing an iconic
photograph never to be forgotten so
you're on a mountain on a hill watching
divers dive into the city center it was
just phenomenal since those days of
course
China's gymnastics has come to the Teddy
heights of Gold's all around since lean
cleanings here of course and now
everyone measures and gives the
benchmark to China for creating the
special special performance
well certainly that reputation has been
enhanced here at these used Olympic
Games we've seen something very special
from wall jumping
you
so we'll be getting the women's 3-meter
springboard victory ceremony in just a
couple of moments and I hope if you were
watching that little montage of walljump
and certainly in the slo-mo the ultra
cam kind of vision that you can just
appreciate how fantastic a wonderfully
disciplined coordinate is beautifully
trained not only she is but others as
well but she is absolutely the queen of
the top very impressive
[Music]
so the woman's 3-meter springboard final
victory ceremony is just about to get
underway and they're the cameras the
eyes everyone is looking at this young
lady Walsh unpin the girl from Nanjing
who has not only done well she has
become champion of the Youth Olympic
Games 3-meter springboard with excellent
performances no one could match her in
terms of her scores
she was sensational
introduction of the VIPs who will make
the presentations but it's a huge moment
here when in Limburg IOC Executive Board
member great privilege for her to be
here in the natatorium and inside the
Olympic sport center
and so the first of the presentations
will be having royalty ie Malaysia there
she is on the right of screen Joey she's
known as a great performance EOS
couldn't quite deliver the final dive
and she knows that she should have had a
silver but a great performance
nevertheless here's the bronze medal to
go with another silver medal from the
10-meter so a really great performance
letter she gets as a souvenir as well
but a fabulous performance for Malaysia
the NOC there will be delighted with
this bronze medal for lo Chaya
well what a fabulous third Daichi hair
the entry you could tell was going to be
delighting everybody catch off it via
coat was delighted with it
he was almost ecstatic with praise and
it proved to be the difference between
bronze and silver for Ghana cost not
schlicht and I tell you she will be
dreaming about that for many many months
if not years if not a lifetime to come
it was extraordinary great work by the
Ukrainian champion for fifty nine point
one was Ghana's score but for ninety two
point zero five was the score of this
young lady war shall offend the gillip
of Nanjing how popular is this from the
Nanking Shuang loose high school just
around the corner she comes through
natatorium here and takes a gold medal
and everyone here was owing and eyeing
how did she manage to be so perfect
fantastic
China gold metal washin thing again
victorious now the national anthem or
the People's Republic of China
[Music]
what an extraordinary achievement she
started competing 2006 eight years ago
her hero is Chun rolling and she wants
to be world champion can you believe
that she won't achieve that an amazing
performance gold medal Worsham thong
silver to ghana fresno sleep and lo sha
yi is the bronze medal winner in the
three meter diving for women
[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]